

CONTACT

- +374 (99) 286 288
- me@armohanyan.dev
- Yerevan Armenia, Komitas 56
- https://armohanyan.dev

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Teamwork
- Time Management

TECHNICAL

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Vue.js
- Nuxt.js
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- MySql
- Postgress
- SQL
- Nginx (basic)
- Apache (basic)

LANGUAGES

- Armenia (Native)
- English (Intermediate)
- Russian (Basics)

ARMEN OHANYAN

STRONG MIDDLE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Hi, I'm Armen Ohanyan, a Fullstack Web Developer with 3-4 years of experience. My main stack is JavaScript, and I'm a strong mid-level developer. I excel in both front-end and back-end development, prioritizing clean, maintainable code and thriving in collaborative environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Iguan Systems

Apr 2022—Present

Full Stack JavaScript developer / Technical Team Leader

- Led a team of developers with a focus on JavaScript, Vue.js, and Node.js.
- Managed project timelines, deliverables, and team performance.
- Developed scalable applications and implemented best practices.
- Coordinated with stakeholders to meet technical requirements and goals.

Upwork Nov 2023—Present

Full Stack JavaScript developer

- Developed responsive web applications using Vue.js, Nuxt.js.
- Built and maintained server-side logic with Node.js and Express.
- Optimized web application performance and ensured cross-device compatibility.
- Utilized Git for version control and participated in agile development practices Configured and managed web servers using Apache and Nginx.

Evistep Enterprise

Oct 2021-Apr 2022

Full Stack PHP developer

- Developed UIs with Vue.js.
- Built applications with Laravel.
- Delivered scalable enterprise solutions.
- Implemented RESTful APIs and used Git for version control.

EDUCATION

National Polytechnic University of Armenia

Software Engineer

National Polytechnic University of Armenia

Cyber Security